Guide to the Herbert L. Abrams Papers SC0858
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-044
  - Politics of Security / Protection (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - References (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - PSR - You Can Make a Difference (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Surival of Nuclear War (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Reliablity Program (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Terrorism Protection (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Abolition - Debate (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dixon: Illusino of Rational Decision-Making (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Advisory Group (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - IPPNW Manuscript (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear War (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Winnable Nuclear War (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Illusion of Long-Term Survival (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Star Wars - Government Reports (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Star Wars - Informed Consent (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Star Wars - ABM Treaty (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Defense (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - MX Missile (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Technology Missiles (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Presidential Control (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Nuclear Football (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Accident and Crises (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Risk Assessment (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Risks and Decisions (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Cognitive Process - Peace (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Crisis Management - Nuclear (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Milgram's Experiments, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Crisis Management - Prevention (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - UN Disarmament Conference (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Crisis Management (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Human Reliablity, Instability (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Reliablity Program (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - FOIA Information (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Power - Risk (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Material (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Waste (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Military Security of Nuclear Arms (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Security - Fuel / Weapons (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Transport (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Theft (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Preventing Accidental Nuclear War (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Accidental Nuclear War (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Building a Bomb (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Effects of Nuclear War (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - On the Psychology of Military Incompetence (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - The Risks of Nuclear Weapons Accidents and Unintentional Nuclear War (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Accidents - General (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Accidents (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Major Accidents (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - S. Plous (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Accidents - Japan (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Accidents - industrial / Vehicular (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Unintentional War (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Preparedness (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Terrorism, 11/19/1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nuclear Power (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Evil (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Evil - References (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Evil - Nuclear References (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Preparedness (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - President Health Course (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - President Health Course (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Health Cont. Ed. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Presidential Helth and Pub. Int. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Conflict of Interest (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Medical Ethics (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Medicare Drug Bill (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Blas (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cost and Efficacy (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondance (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The President has Been Shot, Stanford Press (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Abrams' Angiography, Lippincott Williams and Wilkins (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - College of Physicians of Philiadelphia (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Other proposals (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ins. Of Medicine Prop (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ind Panel Proposals (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Right to Privacy (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Working Group on Disability Clippings and Correspondence, 3/2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - President as Patient (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Malpractice (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - LA Times, "Caution" (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Presidential Health (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Health (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Disability (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Alex George (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - National Security/Conflicts Over Control (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic Monthly (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fatigue of Agining: Aging from Fatigue (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Aging, Fatiguing Originals (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Aging, Cognition (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - European Union (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Japan, Prime Minister (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Cheney - Health (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Cheney (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Cheney (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 12 Year War on Saddam (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Condi Rice (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Holy War of Karl Rove (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Bush National Guard (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Bush and His War (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Doyle 1996 Election (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Starr Report Op Ed (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Secret Service v. Supreme Court (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Reagan Photographs (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - John Hinckley (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Beir VII - Slides, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Caldicot Meeting, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chernobyl, Radition Effects (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fukishima and Chernobyl and Low-level Radiation (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fukishima (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Radition Effect (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hiroshima Study - Stanford Report (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Beir VII - Speech (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IPPNW - History (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Long Term Effects, 2/23/07 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chernobyl Lecture (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - IPPNW - Cont. Ed. Course, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - IPPNW - Hist. Papers (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - IPPNW - Core Curriculum (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Abolition (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IPPNW - Radiation (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IPPNW - First Annual Conference (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - IPPNW - First Congress (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - IPPNW (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - IPPNW Soviet Trip (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - IPPNW Soviet Telecast (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - IPPNW - Andropov Letter (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - IPPNW -Muller's Diary, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - IPPNW - New England Art (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - IPPNW - Linkage Manuscript (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - IPPNW - Nobel Prize (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - IPPNW and Nobel Prize (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Student PSR, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - PSR (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - PSR (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - The Doctor's Dilemma (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Yallow and Teller (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Low Level Radiation (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Bier VII - Low Level Radation (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Nuclear Abolition (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Non-proliferation Gen (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Abolition (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Phase Out (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Test Ban (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NPT and IAEA (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Reg Commission (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The Court's Attack on the Presidency (Transparencies) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Terrorism (General) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chronicle (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Chronicle (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Accidental or Unintentional Nuclear War next year (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Human Fallibility (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Terrorism (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Crisis and Stress (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Human Fallibility: Crisiis and Stress (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Nucelar Energy - Risk (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Nucelar Terrorism (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Nuclear Terrorism (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hiroshima Maidens (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Leitenberg, Milton (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Threat, Weapons Project (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Nuclear Threat (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Nuclear Threat, Pakistan (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Presidents (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Chronicle - Poems (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Black Rat (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - The Black Rat (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Chronicle (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Chronicle - Australia (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Chronicle - Canada (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Chronicle -Cornell (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chronicle - Garland (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Chornicle - Sweden (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Documents Authored by HLA (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Presidents - Washington to Clinton (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Disability - Wislon, Reagan Attacks 1 2 and Clippings, Bush Thyroid Storm (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Terrorism Issues (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Multiple Issues Subjects (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - H.L. Abrams,Author: Nuclear Weapons Accidents I (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Nuclear Weapons Accidents II (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Research on Accidents (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Nuclear War and Weaponry Misc. I (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Chronicle (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - H.L. Abrams, Author: Physicians Movement PSR IPPNW (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Medical Consequences of Nuclear War (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Yale Clippings - Summary of Interviews (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hiroshima, Chernobyl, and Radiation (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Iraq - Timeline and clippings (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - YALTA Book Reviews (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Technological Assessments (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Political Science 138 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Political Science 138 and Related Lectures (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Political Science 138 and Related Lectures (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Randomized Clinical Science (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Magnetic Resonance Imaging (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Political Science 138 and Related Lectures (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - PSR Nobel Prize, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Chronicle, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Various Speeches, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fatigue at Aging, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Book Summaries Related to Yalta (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Publications (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Clinton and the Secret Service - Starr Investigation (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - WP (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - China Chronicle, April 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Chronicle - European Trips, 1958-1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Chronicle, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Health Impairment and Cognition (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Anecdotes (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Human Fallibility in Military and PRP (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Chornicle, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - China, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - H.L. Abrams Author: Effects of Radiation (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - H.L. Abrams Author: Nuclear War Weaponry (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - H.L. Abrams Author: Yalta Conference (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - H.L Abrams Author: Roosevelt Yalta Conference, to the End of Life (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - H.L Abrams Authoer: Presidential Health and Disability (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - H.L. Abrams Author: Presidential Health and Disability (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt at Yalta: A Case Study of the Impact of Disable Leadership on International Relations (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Chronicle (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Medical Malpractice (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Public Interest and the 25th Amendment (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Physician's Responsibility/You Can Make a Difference (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear War Risk, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)